moddingway.com 2017-12-20

# ModdingWay - FIFA 18, NBA 2K18, PES 2018, FIFA 17, NBA 2K17, PES 2017, FIFA 16,FIFA 14, NBA 2K14 Video Games | Mods, Patches, Updates, Downloads

****PRIVACY STATEMENT** **

By visiting or using any document or resouce contained on this website - hereafter to be read as " **http://www.moddingway.com/** " - you agree to be bound by the provisions of these Privacy & User Policies. If at any time you have questions or concerns regarding the information provided by this document, please forward all such discourse to **webmaster@moddingway.com** where the appropriate administrator will respond to you as quickly as possible. **ModdingWay** reserves the right to modify, add, or remove portions of these policies at any time; it is therefore in your best interest to review this document periodically.

*** Information We Collect**

This website is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. This website collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

*** Cookies**

To enhance your online experience we use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. We use cookies to understand Internet usage and to improve our content, offerings, and advertisements. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site, allow you to download files, post comments).

*** Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

*** IP Adresses**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

*** Registration to our Forums**

In order to use our forums, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as gender, location, preferences) so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.

*** Contests and Surveys**

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via contests or surveys. Participation in these surverys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name), and demographic information (age, location). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

*** Newsletter**

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

*** Indemnity**

Although our staff is diligent in providing content that is appropriate to all ages and we screen - to the best of our ability - the content beyond all external links, ModdingWay cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices and/or age specificity of any other website we link to. By viewing ModdingWay you agree not to hold us liable for any damages that may occur by any means or for any reason to yourself or your property.
